alumni.net 2006-12-31

# Alumni.NET - Privacy

**What personal information does Alumni.NET collect?**  
Alumni.NET uses cookies for purposes of saving your email address, password and language preference so you don't have to re-enter it every time to visit the site. Alumni.NET's registration form requires you to input contact and demographic information. This data is used to customize your visit to our site, showing you content that we think you may be interested in. 

**How does Alumni.NET use my Information?**  
Alumni.NET may partner with the alumni association of a given organization. This is indicated by the existence of the organization's official logo beside the organization name on the organization's main page. Under such partnership, Alumni.NET will share its information to the alumni association upon approval of the user. Such approval will make Alumni.NET not liable for any losses or damages suffered because of use or misuse of the information by the alumni association. 

**Alumni.NET and Third Party Advertising**  
Alumni.NET make use of a third-party media company such as DoubleClick's Sonar Network and other third-party advertising companies to display advertising on the site. These ads may contain cookies that the said media company can collect and which Alumni.NET does not have access to. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to Alumni.NET and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements based on goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Does Alumni.NET sell my Information?**  
Alumni.NET will never sell the information in this web site to direct marketers or any other parties without the specific consent of the registrant. Since the service may depend on some advertising revenue, Alumni.NET reserves the right to compile and distribute aggregate information from the alumni registries. 

**How secure are my dealings with Alumni.NET? How secure is Alumni.NET's Technical System?**  
Alumni.NET uses multiple custom-built servers running on secure and reliable OS as well as highly-scalable, enterprise-class mail software. Member data on the servers is stored on RAID sub-systems to ensure integrity, availability, and fast access. All servers are monitored 24 hours a day to ensure maximum uptime and performance. A world-class facility houses the servers, with raised floors, HVAC temperature control systems, seismically braced racks, fire suppression systems, fully redundant power on the premises, and multiple backup generator systems for crisis and disaster protection. 

The facility is connected to the network backbone from multiple sources for the highest level of reliability through BGP (Border Gateway Protocol), which routes information to networks by the shortest and fastest route possible. A 100% network headroom policy is maintained, eliminating the concern for network congestion. This means that additional backbone and intra-network capacity is provisioned when 50% utilization is achieved. The industry standard, closer to 80%, would allow possible line saturation. 

**SPAM Prevention**  
Spamming of members is prevented by a database system that never shows the e-mail addresses of its members. Members are able to send e-mail to each other through the use of website forms. A user can send a maximum of 10 messages a day and his or her e-mail is verified using browser cookies. Only registered members of Alumni.NET may send email to other members of the site. A member may choose, upon registration, to be classified as a private member of an organization, which only allows fellow alumni in the same organization to send him or her an email message. Furthermore, only registered alumni can post articles to or read articles posted on the bulletin board. These measures make it more difficult to abuse the information in this site. However, Alumni.NET shall in no way be liable for any losses or damages suffered because of use or misuse of the site. The policies above are considered accepted when using this website. 

**Photos & Related Links**  
Alumni.NET allows each member to upload one photo. Alumni.NET reserves the right to reject or remove any photos that it deems objectionable or inappropriate for public viewing. The site does not endorse any of the pictures posted. It is the sole responsibility of the member to ensure that the photos posted are not copyrighted, and if they are, the appropriate permissions have been obtained. 

This site contains links to other web sites. Alumni.NET is not responsible for the content or practices of these web sites. 

**How do I change my personal information?**  
Alumni.NET gives users the option of changing or modifying information previously provided. It also allows users to remove their information from the database to not receive email updates about new and updated records in their registered organizations, or to no longer receive Alumni.NET's service. Procedures for deleting or changing user information are given in the Frequently Asked Questions section of the site. 

**What are Alumni.NET's Opt-out policies?**  
Alumni.NET provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from the site at upon registration with the site and at the MyAlumni.NET pages. Visit the site's Help Pages for more information. 

**What else you need to know about your privacy?**  
Please remember that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact **Infophil.COM  
3001-26   
4440 Northwest 73rd Ave.   
Miami, FL 33166-6437   
U.S.A.   
**
